We will go to Garrett Downing at
Baltimore Ravens.com.
>> Hey Jacobe, just uh congratulations
first of all on being a Raven. Um what
are the uh emotions that you have in
getting the call from the Ravens and was
this a team that you felt like could be
a destination for you during this
process?
>> Yeah, thank you Garrett. Nice to meet
you as well. Um definitely wanted to end
up here. I think uh my 30 visit here uh
uh was great. I I enjoyed it uh the most
out of all my 30 visits and uh really
just you know throughout this whole
process I I've or draft uh circuit thing
I've kind of been wishing my name was
called by them so to hear hear it was
was just a blessing and I'm super
grateful.
>> John Han Baltimore Banner
>> congrats. Uh it looks like you have a
lot of people with you. Can you tell us
who is in the house tonight? What was
the reaction when you announced the
news?
>> Yeah, I I definitely was um had a little
bit of a attitude just just waiting for
the call, but um definitely uh was to
myself a little bit, but once I got the
call, everybody started to quiet down.
They kind of knew what time it was. And
uh and then once they found out who it
was, everybody was just pure excitement
as as you would expect. But I think I
think it comes from a place of not
necessarily uh being excited that I'm in
the NFL, but being excited for me as a
person. So super grateful to have them
around me.
>> Pete Gilbert, WB.
>> Jacobe, congratulations and welcome to
Baltimore. I'm curious how much the
Apprentice Gil the relationship you have
with him and you know and on your
meeting and how much you think that may
have affected uh you getting drafted by
Baltimore.
>> Yeah, apprentice is is a great dude.
recruited me when I was 16 years old in
in high school as as well as Casey. Um
uh so just just being able to have that
relationship and not not it it be our
first time meeting I think it was it
already started out on the right foot
and then you know just just getting in
the building getting around guys and and
really um being able to mix and mingle
it I think that's what really set it
apart. So, um I and of course
apprentice. So, I I can't can't I can't
even put into words how grateful I am
for him. Uh and I I I'll definitely do
him a song. So,
>> Brian Wacker, Baltimore Sun.
>> Hey, Jacobe. Congrats, man. Um just two
quick things. How um how much forward
are you looking to playing with Lamar
Jackson, of course, and it sounds like,
you know, you kind of thought you'd go a
little bit higher? Just how much will
that I guess motivate you?
>> Yeah, not necessarily think I would go
higher, but just the anticipation of of
waiting, you know, uh not knowing when
or or where the call is going to be
from. I think that that was where it
came from rather than having an attitude
not hearing my name called. Um, but but
catching catching passes from Lamar
Jackson that if that doesn't put a smile
on your face, I don't know what will.
And then in that same sense, if if he
turns on the Jets and gets past the line
of scrimmage, I'll be sure to get it get
on my man and block down the field. So,
super grateful for this opportunity.
I'll make sure to make the most of it
wherever wherever that opportunity
comes. So,
>> we'll go Ryan Mink of Baltimore
Ravens.com and then Jeff Zerbeck of the
Athletic.
Jacobe, your your highlight reel is just
littered with one-handed catches in the
end zone. Can you talk about your
mindset as kind of that jump ball kind
of guy down uh down in the red zone?
>> Yeah, definitely having that that in my
bag and being able to go up and and go
get those balls that are are are up top.
But I think above everything else, I
think I am a a great wide receiver that
has a lot of traits besides a jump ball.
And I I'm excited to be able to show
that and bring that to Baltimore and um
as well as a bunch of other traits, but
as soon as that ball's in the air, you
can you can guarantee it's coming down
with me. So
Jeff and then Child's Walker,
>> Jacobe, what you mentioned how the 30
visit with the Ravens kind of felt
unique other than Apprentice. What made
it feel that way? what was so unique
about it and made you have such a good
feeling when you exited their facility?
>> Yeah, you know, just just talking with
guys like Azie and and you know, not
really feeling like it was a job and
more more feeling like it was it was an
opportunity to just talk and and and
share my experience of of my my life and
my my football experience. So, I think a
lot of times it felt like I was in a job
interview in these situations when when
I was in in Baltimore. It really felt
like um a place that I could I could get
used to. So, just just super grateful
that they they welcome me with open arms
and I can really really perceive that.
So,
>> yeah. Hey, Jacobe. Uh congratulations.
Um you you said you feel like you're
already an all-around wide receiver, but
I guess where where do you feel like you
have still have the most room to grow?
Yeah, I don't think there's one certain
area that I would say more than any
other, but I think the top of the route
releases, um, blocking downfield,
they're they're all areas where I look
to get better in, as well as just the
the necessities like like catching the
ball and and basic route running. I
think, uh, once you start to prioritize
one thing in your game, you kind of lose
sight of other things and and that's one
thing I don't ever want to do. So, being
able to stay loyal to my game and then
prioritize everything, I think that's
that's the way I'll still go.
We'll go Jonas Schaefer with the banner
and then Josh Tolantino with the Sun.
>> Hey Joey, congratulations man. Uh you
mentioned I know you've as been asked
about the 30 bids out already, but um
can you just talk about you know maybe
what you kind of felt you had to prove
to to the Ravens? Like were there kind
of questions that that they asked to you
that are especially memorable that um
you felt like you answered and maybe
kind of helped your case in getting
drafted?
>> Yeah. Uh I don't think it was uh they
were trying to find anything out. I
think they just wanted to see see me in
in person, kind of get a feel for me.
Um, hear my perspective on things, you
know, ask, "Do I love football?" And,
you know, of course, those questions are
more than anything. So, um, just just
being able to get me in the building, I
think, was a big thing for them and kind
of see who I am as a person. And once
they they found out I uh was was a not
necessarily a good fit, but mixed well
with the people in the building, I think
it was good.
And as a quick followup, Patrick, uh,
Jacobe, did you do you have a favorite
uh a f route to run?
>> Fade.
>> Josh Tolantino.
>> Hey, Jacobe. Congratulations, man. Um,
I'm wondering after your 30 visit, um,
what were your initial impressions of of
the meeting offensive coordinator Declan
Doyle? And, you know, one of your former
teammates, Caleb Williams, had a lot of
success, uh, working with him last year.
I guess what did you think of of his
growth and does that, you know,
witnessing a friend or former teammate
excite you about, you know, joining
Declan's offense?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Co coach Doyle has a has a
great plan set for for us and I think
just being able to see where his mind
at. I I think I I was just itching to
play football the whole time I heard him
talking. You know, he has that demeanor
that just that just screams football. I
think um Caleb reiterated that to me. He
said uh he he is a great dude. At the
time, I didn't know if that was where I
was going to end up. So, uh, uh, he he
did say he's a little bit of a not
necessarily a stickler, but, uh, he he
will get on you, and I think that that's
what everybody needs. So, uh, just being
able to get around him during my 30
visit, it just made me even more hungry
to get get around a guy like that, get
coached up hard, and really, uh, grow as
a football player. So, I think being
able to, uh, get introduced to his
offense, uh, with him is is is going to
be a blessing.
We'll close things out with Ryan Mink
from Baltimore Ravens.com.
>> Yeah, Jacobe, I uh see you went to Red
Mountain High School and that Todd Heap
was an assistant coach there. Uh Ravens
legend. Can you talk about the influence
that Todd had on you uh early in your
career?
>> Yeah, Todd is if you've ever been around
Todd, everybody knows he's tenfold the
best human being to really be be around.
And I think just being around him in
high school kind of showed me the ropes
on how to carry myself and and not only
on the field but off the field. And I
think um he he's not only a great mentor
but a damn good football player. So just
being able to be around a guy like that
um even get a little bit of wisdom. I I
think just he he helped me not only grow
as a football player but 10fold as a
man. So, I think uh that guy is not only
a I I hope I can be half the Raven he
was and I so so just to be uh around
him, it's a blessing for sure.
>> Well, Jacobe, we appreciate your time
and congratulations. One thing before we
go, um your friends and family behind
you have been awfully calm and done a
great job. So, if you want to turn
around and have him get loud, go ahead.
Sorry.
>> Thanks, Jacobe. Congratulations.